Patrick J Davis | CV
Web Developer | Bournemouth
Undergraduate | BSc Business I.T.

Website | GitHub | LinkedIn

Mobile Number: 07775690008

Professional Summary

I am an undergraduate in Business Information Technology (Bournemouth University). I have covered elements of business infrastructure, networking, object-oriented-programming, database management, data mining, cloud development, systems and design and more.

I am very interested in web development, regularly following tutorials to improve my knowledge. I am a strong-minded and competent team player. I am reliable, focused and determined to get the job done. I am learning/using both .NET and JS stacks.

Relevant Tech Competency (Other industry-relevant skills are <u>listed on my website</u>) .NET (MVC/Non MVC), C#, Windows Server, SQL

I have experience using these (or similar) technologies personally and professionally. I have experience with Umbraco website development and support. I am familiar with the .NET Core framework. I have studied Udemy courses regarding the fundamentals of .NET and C# to bolster my knowledge.

JavaScript, React, MongoDB, ExpressJS, NodeJS (M.E.R.N. Stack)

I am largely self-taught in this domain and have spent a long time looking into the common 'MERN' stack. I have also studied JavaScript fundamentals through multiple Udemy courses. I have beginners experience with Angular and will soon focus on this technology also.

HTML5, CSS3, JSON, XML, RESTful APIs & more.

I have the fundamental working knowledge for these technologies and basic industry technologies/methods.

Relevant* Work Experience

Greenwood Campbell – Bournemouth – 02/07/2018 - 20/09/2019 – Support Developer

- I was responsible for maintaining legacy projects and helped on some new projects.
- Handling client support requests (bug reports, change requests, new quotes).
- Full stack, with front end work in HTML, CSS, JavaScript JQuery and Back End work using C#,
 .NET & SQL mainly.
- Using and developing Umbraco CMS websites.
- Development of Chatbots & Voice Assistants.

LV= - Bournemouth - 22/07/2018 - 19/09/2019 - Content Editor

• Subcontracted by Greenwood Campbell working for LV=. This involved content work using Sitecore and Continuity C5 CMS. Wireframe creation, content changes and Sprint planning.

*I also have other part/full time experience with non-technical jobs. Though they aren't technical in nature, I'd be happy to discuss them, as they taught me valuable and transferrable skills for any workplace.

Education

Bournemouth University.

• BSc Business Information Technology. Predicted 2/1. 2016-2020.

A Levels at Thetford Grammar School:

Business, I.T. and English Literature. AAA*. 2014-2016.